https://www.renjeau.com/privacy-policy/

Search for:HomeArtistsAll ArtistsContemporary ArtistsTraditional ArtistsArtworkAll ArtContemporary ArtTraditional ArtCustom FramingRestorationConsultingAboutContactContact Info & MapArtist SubmissionsPrivacy Policy
MenuHomeArtistsAll ArtistsContemporary ArtistsTraditional ArtistsArtworkAll ArtContemporary ArtTraditional ArtCustom FramingRestorationConsultingAboutContactContact Info & MapArtist SubmissionsPrivacy Policy
Click here
Renjeau.com Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Renjeau.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Renjeau Galleries | 79 Worcester St. | Natick, MA 01760 | 508-655-5121
| info@renjeau.com | Hours: Monday-Saturday 10-5 Follow Us
Boston-Area Website Design by BKJ Productions
Please notify me of new work tagged as .
Stay informed of new artists, shows, and other gallery events. You can unsubscribe at any time.
Social Distancing OptionsWe are open during our regular hours for browsing fine art or to help you with your custom framing and restoration jobs. We are also continuing to make every effort to accommodate you remotely if you prefer.  If you see artwork on our website which you would like to purchase or try on approval in your home, please let us know.We hope to hear from you soon!Inquire For PricePlease complete the form below, or call us at 508-655-5121
Search View In PersonPlease contact us to view this piece in the gallery. We may also be able to arrange for you to see this piece in your home. Fill in the form below or call us at 508-655-5121. View on My WallPlease upload photo of your space, and we will create a virtual rendering of this artwork on your wall and email you back an image usually within 24 hours. Please take photo from a distance in order to view context of room.
